<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carlie Hamilton</title>
    <description>Personal website</description>
    <link>http://carlie.rocks</link>
    <atom:link href="http://carlie.rocks/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 28 - Starting PostgreSQL!</title>
        <description>
          
          100 Days of Code Worked On Learning PostgreSQL on the command line Progress Today with school I started learning PostgreSQL. We learnt a bit of PGAdmin 4, but… I don’t like it 😆 It requires you to use the mouse too much, which I find irritating, so I’ve been spending...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-28-psql/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-28-psql/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 24 - 27: Working on my Portfolio</title>
        <description>
          
          100 Days of Code Worked On My portfolio! Progress I’ve been coding my portfolio. Oh, my portfolio. I am frustrated because my expectations are at 100 - I really want to have something professional out there with my name on it - but I don’t know if I have the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/portfolio/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/portfolio/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 23: SASS</title>
        <description>
          
          100 Days of Code Worked On Learn sass, mixins, variables, etc. Very cool. I like it a lot, as far as liking css goes. I… I know CSS, I can do the CSS, and hell, I enjoy creating my own websites. But I much prefer the challenge of coding. Looking...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-23-sass/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-23-sass/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 22: Sorting Algorithms</title>
        <description>
          
          100 Days of Code Worked On Ruby Challenge 21 - Sort Numbers Ruby Challenge 22 - Exes and Ohs Ruby Challenge 23 - First Non Repeating Ruby Challenge 24 - Isogram Ruby Challenge 25 - Remove Adjacent Duplicates Ruby Challenge 26 - Max Min Ruby Challenge 27 - In Array...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-22/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-22/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 21: Starting My Portfolio</title>
        <description>
          
          100 Days of Code Worked On Started working on my portfolio! I haven’t done much, taking it slow because I haven’t learnt sass yet. But, I have started a mood board. Because I’ve switched to linux, I’ve been using gimp and I have no idea what I’m doing. I miss...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-21-portfolio/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-21-portfolio/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 20: Linux Installed</title>
        <description>
          
          100 Days of Code Worked On Linux is now installed on my machine. Windows is gone! So far I am enjoying the experience and a fresh start, but it is a bit of a pain in the arse trying to get all the things reinstalled. My biggest annoyance - and...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-20-installed-linux/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-20-installed-linux/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 19: QtPy5 GUI for my Music App</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On My Music App - creating a GUI with QtPy5 Progress Before I started the 100 Days of Code - and before I started the course I am doing - I was learning/practicing using APIs and Python with some scripts that did various things with spotify. My idea was...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-19-qtpy5-gui-for-my-music-app/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/day-19-qtpy5-gui-for-my-music-app/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 18: Blog Deployment</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On This blog! I uploaded the Jekyll version Got not one but two solutions to daily challenge 19! Progress Today I finished converting all my previous blog posts to Jekyll, and uploaded it live live live! It is not my final solution for a blog. I either want to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/jekyll/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 17: Speech</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Worked on this website a little bit, and then did my first speech! I did a speech on Vim basics. My proposal was that people should start using vim with the extension in VS Code (or whatever text editor/IDE they use). That way you have a lower barrier...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/speech/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/speech/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 16: Flask and Jekyll</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Flask Microblog lessons 4 &amp;amp; 5 SQLAlchemy Jekyll Installation on my local computer Progress So, I think I’m going to try to turn this blog into a Jekyll blog. See how that goes… Oh, I’m writing this entry in vim! Never would have guessed I’d be doing this...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/jekyll/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 15: Starting a Microblog</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Creating a Microblog with the Flask Mega Tutorial - completed lesson 3 Progress OK, so on Monday and Tuesday I had assessment at school, so technically I was doing some coding stuff. But honestly I’d rather forget all that. So, instead, today is day 15. We have started...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/flask-microblog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/flask-microblog/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 14. How to Blog</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Thinking about this website Progress I’ve been thinking a bit about this website today. I really want to make my own blogging CMS. Yes, I know there are lots of options out there. I have used many. But I am looking forward to the challenge of making my...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/flask/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/flask/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 13: Slowly Recovering</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Completed Ruby Challenges - completed 16 - 18, and also refactored 14 &amp;amp; 15 Progress Still so burnt out from the assignment, I feel like I can’t do anything exciting, even though I’d really like to work on my music app. Instead, late at night, I managed to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/recovering/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/recovering/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 11 &amp; 12: Working on Assignment</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On


  Purr Seasons Cat Hotel - class assignment, ruby terminal app.




Progress

Working on my assignment. On a tight deadline. Now I don’t want to even look at the code to see all the things we (my teammate and I) could have done better. It is done.

        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/assignment/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/assignment/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 10: Updating Progress</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Terminal Medication Tracker Progress The days have passed and I have only really missed one day where I have done 0 coding, but I have missed recording here. It’s too much trouble to go back, so I’m just going forward and calling today day 10. I do have...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/updating/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/updating/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 9: TDD</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Daily Challenge - Hackerman Redo Challenge - FizzBuzz Progress Class today (what I heard - I was home with a sick kid) was about Test Driven Development, and it made a lot of sense. I already do this but in a really informal way. And, of course, up...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/tdd/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/tdd/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 8: Sssssssnake!</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Snake game! Progress Today I made a minimum viable snake game! There are a lot of features to add, but the game works! The thing I had the most trouble with was just getting the syntax right for the randomly spawning food - I kept on leaving a...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/snake/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/snake/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 7: Started Snake</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Daily Coding Challenge - Fibonacci Snake Game Progress The kids are sick. I hope I don’t get sick… Plus I’ve been feeling a bit burnt out and deflated by my attempt at using classes to create my cafe app. I needed something fun. But what? I was having...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/snake/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/snake/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 6: Just some exercises</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Done with my cafe Challenge 12 - Count Words Challenge 9 - Vowels Progress I said I was done with my cafe, but then I made some small changes. First, I just made it so that it doesn’t matter how many items you add to the cafe, you...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/exercises/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/exercises/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 5: Backing Away Slowly from the Cafe</title>
        <description>
          
          Worked On Cafe Ordering Script Used a fellow classmate’s code to update my name generator, and then did my first pull request! Daily Challenge - FizzBuzz Progress That cafe script. My problem is trying to access information which is a (and I’ll probably use the wrong terminology here) a class...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/cafe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://carlie.rocks/developer/2019/cafe/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
